KtaneTheWeakestLinkData = {
  "CharacterNames": [
    "John",
    "William",
    "James",
    "Charles",
    "George",
    "Frank",
    "Joseph",
    "Thomas",
    "Henry",
    "Robert",
    "Edward",
    "Harry",
    "Walter",
    "Arthur",
    "Fred",
    "Albert",
    "Samuel",
    "David",
    "Louis",
    "Joe",
    "Charlie",
    "Clarence",
    "Richard",
    "Andrew",
    "Daniel",
    "Ernest",
    "Will",
    "Jesse",
    "Oscar",
    "Lewis",
    "Peter",
    "Benjamin",
    "Frederick",
    "Willie",
    "Alfred",
    "Sam",
    "Roy",
    "Herbert",
    "Jacob",
    "Tom",
    "Elmer",
    "Carl",
    "Lee",
    "Howard",
    "Martin",
    "Michael",
    "Bert",
    "Herman",
    "Jim",
    "Francis",
    "Mary",
    "Anna",
    "Emma",
    "Elizabeth",
    "Minnie",
    "Margaret",
    "Ida",
    "Alice",
    "Bertha",
    "Sarah",
    "Annie",
    "Clara",
    "Ella",
    "Florence",
    "Cora",
    "Martha",
    "Laura",
    "Nellie",
    "Grace",
    "Carrie",
    "Maude",
    "Mabel",
    "Bessie",
    "Jennie",
    "Gertrude",
    "Julia",
    "Hattie",
    "Edith",
    "Mattie",
    "Rose",
    "Catherine",
    "Lillian",
    "Ada",
    "Lillie",
    "Helen",
    "Jessie",
    "Louise",
    "Ethel",
    "Lula",
    "Myrtle",
    "Eva",
    "Frances",
    "Lena",
    "Lucy",
    "Edna",
    "Maggie",
    "Pearl",
    "Daisy",
    "Fannie",
    "Josephine"
  ],
  "QuizBank": [
    {
      "Question": "What is a boss module that is red and has numbered keys 0-9 with a stage counter on the right and number on a wide display on the bottom?",
      "Answers": ["Forget Me Not"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Forget Everything"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "“MAZE GAMER” and “HELP IM LOST” are phrases from what module?",
      "Answers": ["3D Maze"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Crazy Talk"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What enemy from Adventure Game has the strongest stats?",
      "Answers": ["Demon"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "Dragon",
        "Eagle",
        "Goblin",
        "Golem",
        "Troll",
        "Lizard",
        "Wizard"
      ],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which position in Chess is always a rook",
      "Answers": ["4th"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1st"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What does S mean from Color Math?",
      "Answers": ["Subtract", "Subtraction"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["sin"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What colour is the switch in Crazy Talk?",
      "Answers": ["Yellow"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Green"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What two elements do you combine to make Life in Creation?",
      "Answers": ["Energy and Swamp", "Swamp and Energy"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Fire and Air"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the title of the excerpt used in Cryptography?",
      "Answers": ["A Christmas Carol"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Carols of the Bells"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What colour is the text in English Test?",
      "Answers": ["Green"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Yellow"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What numbers does a number have to be divisible by for the answer to be FizzBuzz in Fizzbuzz?",
      "Answers": ["3 and 5", "5 and 3"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["5 and 7"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What colour is the submit button from Friendship?",
      "Answers": ["Blue", "Cyan", "Aqua"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Purple"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which shape from Hexamaze is rotated four different ways?",
      "Answers": ["Triangle"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Hexagon"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which parity does the minutes have to be to submit an answer in Ice Cream?",
      "Answers": ["Even"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Odd"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What letter do you press if the number is sixty-nine in Letter Keys?",
      "Answers": ["D"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["A", "B", "C"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many colours are present in Light Cycle?",
      "Answers": ["6"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which button position is the dollar sign in Listening?",
      "Answers": ["2nd"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1ST", "3RD", "4TH"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What does the red LED mean in Logic?",
      "Answers": ["NOT"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["On"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many colour codes are there in Microcontroller?",
      "Answers": ["6"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Modules Against Humanity, what word does a card need to spell to have it set at position Two?",
      "Answers": ["Poop"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Pee", "Crap"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many possible rooms are there in Murder?",
      "Answers": ["9"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many possible mazes are there in Mouse in the Maze?",
      "Answers": ["6"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Mystic Square, which tile is the skull hidden under if the centre space starts off as empty?",
      "Answers": ["7"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What colour is the eye in Orientation Cube?",
      "Answers": ["Blue"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Green"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the only letter that has an umlaut in Password Translated German?",
      "Answers": ["U"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "A",
        "B",
        "C",
        "D",
        "E",
        "F",
        "G",
        "H",
        "I",
        "J",
        "K",
        "L",
        "M",
        "N",
        "O",
        "P",
        "Q",
        "R",
        "S",
        "T",
        "V",
        "W",
        "X",
        "Y",
        "Z"
      ],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many keys are there to press in Piano Keys?",
      "Answers": ["12"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What colour do the pipes turn into when Plumbing is solved?",
      "Answers": ["Blue"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Green"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many cards are in the initial sequence in Point of Order?",
      "Answers": ["5"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many buttons are present in Round Keypad?",
      "Answers": ["8"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which face of the Rubik’s Cube is unused to get the answer for Rubik’s Cube?",
      "Answers": ["Back"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Down"],
      "Category": ""
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many positions does each dial have in Safety Safe?",
      "Answers": ["12"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which position does the screw start in The Screw?",
      "Answers": ["Top Left", "1st"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "Top Middle",
        "Top Right",
        "Middle Left",
        "Center",
        "Middle Right",
        "Bottom Left",
        "Bottom Middle",
        "Bottom Right",
        "2nd",
        "3rd",
        "4th",
        "5th",
        "6th"
      ],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many possible shapes are there in Shape Shift? ",
      "Answers": ["16"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many possible keywords are there in Silly Slots?",
      "Answers": ["7"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many adjacent colours need to flash in clockwise order to satisfy the first condition in Simon Screams?",
      "Answers": ["3"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which position colour do you need for the priority list in Simon States?",
      "Answers": ["Top Left"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Top Right", "Bottom Left", "Bottom Right"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which Switch is the one where if it was the only one up, would it be an illegal position in Switches?",
      "Answers": ["3", "3rd"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1st", "2nd", "4th", "5th", "1", "2", "4", "5"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Where is the status light in Third Base?",
      "Answers": ["Bottom Left"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Top left", "top right", "bottom right"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What colour is the pass button in Tic Tac Toe?",
      "Answers": ["Red"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Blue"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What colour is the text displayed in Two Bits?",
      "Answers": ["Yellow"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Black"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What coordinate do you need for the list of valid coordinates in Wire Placement?",
      "Answers": ["C3"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "A1",
        "B1",
        "C1",
        "D1",
        "A2",
        "B2",
        "C2",
        "D2",
        "A3",
        "B3",
        "D3",
        "A4",
        "B4",
        "C4",
        "D4"
      ],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Yahtzee, you keep the outlier if your first roll is what? ",
      "Answers": ["Small Straight"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Full house", "Pair", "2 pairs"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many animals are present when opening the door in Zoo?",
      "Answers": ["6"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which key do you turn first in Turn the Keys?",
      "Answers": ["Right"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Left", "Both"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In KTANE, what is the name of the main font used in manuals?",
      "Answers": ["Special Elite"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Arial", "Comic Sans"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Replace any 2 with a 5 and any 7 with a 0. What module does this?",
      "Answers": ["Skewed Slots"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Yahtzee", "Ice Cream", "Point of Order", "Minesweeper"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What module has a 4 by 3 grid of letters and a green submit button?",
      "Answers": ["Adjacent Letters"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Battleship"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What module does a beggar come from?",
      "Answers": ["Garnet Thief"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Lion share"],
      "Category": ""
    },
    {
      "Question": "Seated and Teased, what other word can you spell in Anagrams?",
      "Answers": ["Sedate"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Seat"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "From Astrology, what is the symbol with a triangle facing down called?",
      "Answers": ["Water"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Air", "Fire", "Earth"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "R9 gets what battleship coordinate radar?",
      "Answers": ["C4"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "A1",
        "B1",
        "C1",
        "D1",
        "E1",
        "A2",
        "B2",
        "C2",
        "D2",
        "E2",
        "A3",
        "B3",
        "C3",
        "D3",
        "E3",
        "A4",
        "B4",
        "D4",
        "E4",
        "A5",
        "B5",
        "C5",
        "D5",
        "E5"
      ],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Battleship, ports are used as the letter, batteries and ____ are used as the number.",
      "Answers": ["Indicators"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Port plates"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many LEDS are on the module Binary LEDS?",
      "Answers": ["5"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many total cells are in the module Bitmaps?",
      "Answers": ["64"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["40", "63", "32"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What button is mentioned in the first condition in Broken Buttons?",
      "Answers": ["Sea"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["See"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What do you do first when the bulb is OFF in The Bulb?",
      "Answers": ["Unscrew"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Press I", "Press O"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "All fruits are 25% more per pound on what day in Cheap Checkout",
      "Answers": ["Friday"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "Sunday",
        "Monday",
        "Tuesday",
        "Wednesday",
        "Thursday",
        "Saturday"
      ],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Lines, Arrows, and WHAT are possible hand shapes from The Clock",
      "Answers": ["Spades"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Hearts"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many displays flash on a Colour Flash?",
      "Answers": ["8"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What variable do you need for the second in Combination Lock?",
      "Answers": ["Number of Modules"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Number of indicators"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Where is A-1 in Coordinates?",
      "Answers": ["Bottom Left"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Top Left"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What corner on the display in Double-Oh is the dot located?",
      "Answers": ["Bottom Right"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["bottom left", "Top Left", "top right"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many seconds do you have to submit each answer in Fast Math?",
      "Answers": ["10"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What port is mentioned for the first condition of the starting wire in Follow the Leader?",
      "Answers": ["RJ", "RJ-45"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Parallel", "Stero RCA", "PS/2", "DVI-D", "Serial"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the currency CNY stands for in Foreign Exchange Rates?",
      "Answers": ["Chinese Yuan"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Yen"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What does the number have to be for the first condition to apply for each subcommand in The Gamepad?",
      "Answers": ["Prime"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Even", "Odd"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Bitwise Operations, AND OR XOR and what else are possible logic gates?",
      "Answers": ["NOT"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["NAND", "NOR", "XNOR"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "SEMTEX is an answer from what module?",
      "Answers": ["Word Scramble"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Caesar Cipher"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If there is an even number of batteries, what section do you press in Blind Alley?",
      "Answers": ["Center"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "top left",
        "top middle",
        "top right",
        "middle left",
        "middle right",
        "bottom left",
        "bottom middle",
        "bottom right"
      ],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "(A NOR B) AND C. What is the only correct answer from Boolean Venn Diagram?",
      "Answers": ["C"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["ABC"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What edgework do you need to get a 0 Caesar shift condition from Caesar Cipher?",
      "Answers": ["Parallel and Lit NSA", "Lit NSA and Parallel"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "lit SND and parallel",
        "lit CLR and parallel",
        "lit CAR and parallel",
        "lit IND and parallel",
        "lit FRQ and parallel",
        "lit SIG and parallel",
        "lit MSA and parallel",
        "lit TRN and parallel",
        "lit BOB and parallel",
        "lit FRK and parallel"
      ],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Chord Qualities, which chord has a distance of 3 4 3 2?",
      "Answers": ["-7"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "-Δ7♯5",
        "Δ7♯5",
        "ø",
        "-add9",
        "Δ7",
        "7♯9",
        "7sus",
        "add9",
        "7",
        "-Δ7",
        "7♯5"
      ],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If the numbers on Connection Check are all different, what character from the serial number do you use?",
      "Answers": ["6th", "Last"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1ST", "2ND", "3RD", "4TH", "5TH"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What does the symbol with a circle inside a square mean in Laundry?",
      "Answers": ["Tumble Dry"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["low heat", "medium heat", "high heat", "no heat"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the multiplier for orange in LED Encryption?",
      "Answers": ["7"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["2", "3", "4", "5", "6"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many columns are in the grid in Minesweeper?",
      "Answers": ["6"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What colour is Bob’s shirt in Monsplode Fight!?",
      "Answers": ["Blue"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Red", "Orange", "Yellow", "Green", "Purple"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Morse, what does - - - - translate to?",
      "Answers": ["CH"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "A",
        "B",
        "C",
        "D",
        "E",
        "F",
        "G",
        "H",
        "I",
        "J",
        "K",
        "L",
        "M",
        "N",
        "O",
        "P",
        "Q",
        "R",
        "S",
        "T",
        "U",
        "V",
        "W",
        "X",
        "Y",
        "Z"
      ],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "“If A + B is square, +4 to A” is a condition from what module?",
      "Answers": ["Morsematics"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Colored Squares"],
      "Category": ""
    },
    {
      "Question": "What does NH3 mean in Neutralization?",
      "Answers": ["Ammonia"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "Lithium hydroxide",
        "Sodium hydroxide",
        "Potassium hydroxide"
      ],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If the sum of all the digits in the code is _____, reverse the code in Number Pad.",
      "Answers": ["Even"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Prime", "Odd"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The dotless i is only unique to which language in Only Connect?",
      "Answers": ["Turkish"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["English", "French", "German", "Polish"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many prime sequences are in each table in Perspective Pegs?",
      "Answers": ["8"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What position is the red and white coloured wire located in Probing?",
      "Answers": ["1", "1st"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "2",
        "3",
        "4",
        "5",
        "6",
        "2nd",
        "3rd",
        "4th",
        "5th",
        "6th"
      ],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Where are the sixteenth notes located in Rhythms?",
      "Answers": ["Bottom Right"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["top left", "top right", "bottom left"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "“Skip this row if the serial number contains X or Y” is a condition from what module?",
      "Answers": [
        "Rock-Paper-Scissors-Lizard-Spock",
        "Rock Paper Scissors Lizard Spock",
        "RPSLS"
      ],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Neutralization", "Monsplode, Fight!", "Light Cycle"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What end phrase does burger belong to in Sea Shells?",
      "Answers": ["On the Seesaw"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "ON THE SEA SHORE",
        "ON THE SHE SORE",
        "ON THE SHE SURE"
      ],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "When the LED is flickering cyan, what multiplier of the total number of seconds do you release the Square Button on?",
      "Answers": ["7"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "KTANE"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The road signs in the UK that warn the road user are of what geometric shape?",
      "Answers": ["Triangular", "Triangle"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Square", "Circular", "Diamond"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The island of Sri Lanka lies off the coast of which Asian country?",
      "Answers": ["India"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Sadi Arabia", "Bangladesh", "Mongolia"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What 'P' is the Spanish word for quick and is used in English to mean 'at once'?",
      "Answers": ["Pronto"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Por favor", "Rapido", "Pinto"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Tunis is the capital city of which North African country?",
      "Answers": ["Tunisia"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Ghana", "Mali", "Morocco"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which is the largest and most heavily populated island in the Mediterranean sea?",
      "Answers": ["Sicily"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Puerto Rico", "Carribieans", "Cyprus"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The (UK) National Space Centre is based in which Midlands city?",
      "Answers": ["Leicester"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Venice", "Berlin", "Belgium"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Cantonese and Mandarin are languages which originated in which country?",
      "Answers": ["China"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Japan", "Russia", "The Philippines"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Leibfraumilch is a wine produced in which European country?",
      "Answers": ["Germany"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Belgium", "Switzerland"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Mount Olympus is the highest mountain in which European country? ",
      "Answers": ["Greece"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["France", "Russia", "Lithuania"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which oriental country shares its name with a type of porcelain?",
      "Answers": ["China"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Portugal"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What 'K' is the currency of Sweden?",
      "Answers": ["Krone"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Euros"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the capital of Iraq?",
      "Answers": ["Baghdad"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Erbil", "Ramadi", "Mosul", "Basrah", "Hillah"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which German city is also the name of a type of perfume?",
      "Answers": ["Cologne"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Brussels", "Berlin"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The equator divides the world into how many hemispheres?",
      "Answers": ["2"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which South American country has borders with ten others?",
      "Answers": ["Brazil"],
      "WrongAnswers": [" Argentina", "Colombia", "Peru", "Chile"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In the UK, which product had an advertising ban imposed on it in 1999?",
      "Answers": ["Tobacco"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Cocaine", "Butter Fingers", "Perfume"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What 'U' is a South American country whose capital is Montevideo?",
      "Answers": ["Uruguay"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Brazil", "Guatemala", "Chile", "Argentina"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The city of Tallinn is the capital of which of the Baltic states?",
      "Answers": ["Estonia"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Sweden", "Norway", "Finland"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Sudan is the largest country in which continent?",
      "Answers": ["Africa"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Asia"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The towns of El Paso and San Antonio are in which US state",
      "Answers": ["Texas"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["South America"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What North African country beginning with the letter L has a plain green flag?",
      "Answers": ["Libya"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Lithuania "],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The ancient site known as the Valley of the Kings is in which country?",
      "Answers": ["Egypt"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["England", "China", "Thailand", "Japan", "Korea"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the standard geometric shape of a U.S stop sign?",
      "Answers": ["Octagon"],
      "WrongAnswers": [" Hexagon"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the largest lake in the world?",
      "Answers": ["Caspian Sea", "Caspian"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Black Sea"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which continent experiences the majority of the natural occurrence of tornados?",
      "Answers": ["North America"],
      "WrongAnswers": [" South America"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many major named waterfalls make up the Niagara Falls waterfall complex?",
      "Answers": ["3"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Mount Everet is located in which country?",
      "Answers": ["Nepal"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Sylvania"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the national animal of Scotland?",
      "Answers": ["Unicorn"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Bear", "Snake", "Bagpipes", "Moose", "Axolotl"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "After 1911, what animal is prominently featured on the state flag of California?",
      "Answers": ["Bear"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Unicorn"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which continent would you have to travel to if you want to see a hippo in the wild?",
      "Answers": ["Africa"],
      "WrongAnswers": [" South America"],
      "Category": ""
    },
    {
      "Question": "What isolated African nation has the highest rate of endemism in the world?",
      "Answers": ["Madagascar"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Nigeria", "South Africa", "Ethiopia"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the most populous city in the world?",
      "Answers": ["Tokyo"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["New Delhi", "Beijing", "Mumbai"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which country has the most pyramids?",
      "Answers": ["Sudan"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Egypt", "England", "India", "Myanmar"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many countries does Africa have?",
      "Answers": ["54"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["72", "57"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the capital of Senegal?",
      "Answers": ["Darkar"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Synagogue"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which continent does Guyana lie?",
      "Answers": ["South America"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Africa"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which city was the capital of New Zealand until it was replaced by Wellington?",
      "Answers": ["Auckland"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Sydney", "Old Zealand"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In America, the Golden Gate Bridge is a feature of which city? ",
      "Answers": ["San Francisco"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["New York"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Vietnam has land borders with Laos, Cambodia and which other country? ",
      "Answers": ["China"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Thailand"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What was the first name of the German composer Bach, who was born in 1685?",
      "Answers": ["Johann"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Adolf", "Chopin"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which city was chosen to host the first Chinese Grand Prix?",
      "Answers": ["Shanghai"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Beijing"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which country is made up of 7,000 islands?",
      "Answers": ["The Philippines"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "The United States",
        "Australia",
        "Oceania",
        "Indonesia",
        "Hawaii",
        "Japan",
        "Malaysia"
      ],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which country lies roughly 90 miles southeast of Florida?",
      "Answers": ["Cuba"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Dominican Republic"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the capital of the United Kingdom?",
      "Answers": ["London"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["UK"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the capital of Italy?",
      "Answers": ["Rome"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Venice", "Melin", "Maples"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which of these countries has the smallest population: France, United Kingdom, or Spain?",
      "Answers": ["Spain"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["United Kingdom", "Pain"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the capital of Hungary?",
      "Answers": ["Budapest"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Thirsty"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the currency used in India?",
      "Answers": ["Rupee"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Zelda"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the third most-spoken language in Canada?",
      "Answers": ["Chinese", "Mandarin", "Chinese Mandarin"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["French", "English", "Spanish"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Morocco has two official languages: Tamazight and what?",
      "Answers": ["Arabic"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Moroccan", "English", "Afrikaans"],
      "Category": "Geography"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What word means the order of lessons in schools and the running of trains and buses? ",
      "Answers": ["Timetable"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["automobile", "period"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What 'X' is the fear of foreigners or strangers?",
      "Answers": ["Xenophobia"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["The X-Factor"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In the modern English alphabet, which is the penultimate letter",
      "Answers": ["Y"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "A",
        "B",
        "C",
        "D",
        "E",
        "F",
        "G",
        "H",
        "I",
        "J",
        "K",
        "L",
        "M",
        "N",
        "O",
        "P",
        "Q",
        "R",
        "S",
        "T",
        "U",
        "V",
        "W",
        "X",
        "Z"
      ],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What word can mean touch-down of an aeroplane or the level floor between two staircases?",
      "Answers": ["Landing"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Step"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A person who earns just enough for basic needs is said to live 'hand to ..' what?",
      "Answers": ["Mouth"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Frugal", "hand"],
      "Category": ""
    },
    {
      "Question": "What 'B' is another name for the American Buffalo?",
      "Answers": ["Bison"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Beeffalo", "Boar"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which 'H' means the emergence of young creatures from eggs",
      "Answers": ["Hatching"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Hernia"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What word for the past tense of 'rise' is also a widely cultivated flower?",
      "Answers": ["Rose"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Risen", "rizz"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Weight-lifting is also known as 'pumping..' what metal?",
      "Answers": ["Iron"],
      "WrongAnswers": [" Steel"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What word meaning chilly goes before snap, front and spell in weather forecasting?",
      "Answers": ["Cold"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Freezing"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What word follows record, designer and luggage to form three other phrases?",
      "Answers": ["Collection"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Airport"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What word that means 'existing' precedes 'room' and is another name for the lounge in a house",
      "Answers": ["Living"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Live", "Life"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the name of the large absorbent cloth used to dry the body after a bath or shower? ",
      "Answers": ["Towel", "Rag"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Shamwow", "Scrub daddy"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the three-letter name of the area which is the background for the sun, moon and stars?",
      "Answers": ["Sky"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Base", "Background", "Wallpaper"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If 'oversteer' makes a car take a bend too sharply, what makes a car go straight?",
      "Answers": ["Understeer"],
      "WrongAnswers": [" Holding the steering wheel straight", "Inertia"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The word 'ape' is an anagram of which small vegetable?",
      "Answers": ["Pea"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Ape", "Apple", "Anagram"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What word that means 'the same all over' is the name given to the clothes worn by the police and the armed services?",
      "Answers": ["Uniform"],
      "WrongAnswers": [" Unicorn", "Same"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which three-letter word means to cut grass?",
      "Answers": ["Mow"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Cut"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What letter in the modern alphabet lies between P and R?",
      "Answers": ["Q"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "A",
        "B",
        "C",
        "D",
        "E",
        "F",
        "G",
        "H",
        "I",
        "J",
        "K",
        "L",
        "M",
        "N",
        "O",
        "P",
        "R",
        "S",
        "T",
        "U",
        "V",
        "W",
        "X",
        "Y",
        "Z"
      ],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "'Bolster' is an anagram of which sea crustacean?",
      "Answers": ["Lobster"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Crab"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which three-letter word is known as 'the definite article'?",
      "Answers": ["The"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Def", "An"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In a family what 'O' describes a child with no brothers or sisters?",
      "Answers": ["Only"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Orphan"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In proverbs, which big cat is said to be unable to change its spots?",
      "Answers": ["Leopard"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Cheetah", "Tiger"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "According to tradition, the consumption of which fruit a day keeps the doctor away?",
      "Answers": ["Apple"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Date"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "When commuters travel on crowded trains they are frequently said to be packed in like what fish?",
      "Answers": ["Sardines"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Eels"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the three letter word for the outside edge of a wheel?",
      "Answers": ["Rim"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Hubcap"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which letter in the word 'colour' is not used in the American spelling?",
      "Answers": ["U"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["O", "R"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What 'D' is a language that is no longer spoken?",
      "Answers": ["Dead"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Extinct"],
      "Category": ""
    },
    {
      "Question": "In English editions of Scrabble, which letter is worth 5 points?",
      "Answers": ["K"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "A",
        "B",
        "C",
        "D",
        "E",
        "F",
        "G",
        "H",
        "I",
        "J",
        "L",
        "M",
        "N",
        "O",
        "P",
        "Q",
        "R",
        "S",
        "T",
        "U",
        "V",
        "W",
        "X",
        "Y",
        "Z"
      ],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Somnambulating is a fancy term for what nighttime activity?",
      "Answers": ["Sleepwalking"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Skinny dipping"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What common Latin phrase literally means “something for something”",
      "Answers": ["Quid Pro Quo"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["sum fo sum"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What word signifies the “art and technique of arranging type to make written language legible, readable, and appealing”?",
      "Answers": ["Typography"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Graphic Design"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the name of the international Language Arts competition for students in grades 3 - 8 which has thrice annual challenges of twenty analogies?",
      "Answers": ["WordMasters"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Spelling Bee"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In American Sign Language, closing your hand into a fist with your thumb resting across the front of a couple fingers represents what letter in the alphabet?",
      "Answers": ["S"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "A",
        "B",
        "C",
        "D",
        "E",
        "F",
        "G",
        "H",
        "I",
        "J",
        "K",
        "L",
        "M",
        "N",
        "O",
        "P",
        "Q",
        "R",
        "T",
        "U",
        "V",
        "W",
        "X",
        "Y",
        "Z"
      ],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which of the following is not considered a romance language? Italian, French, English, Spanish, Portuguese, Latin?",
      "Answers": ["English"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Italian", "French", "Spanish", "Portuguese", "Latin"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the British term for a flashlight?",
      "Answers": ["Torch"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Lantern", "lamp"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In the International Phonetic Alphabet, an unstressed central vowel is called a “schwa”, and is represented by what lowercase letter, upside down?",
      "Answers": ["E"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "A",
        "B",
        "C",
        "D",
        "E",
        "F",
        "G",
        "H",
        "I",
        "J",
        "K",
        "L",
        "M",
        "N",
        "O",
        "P",
        "Q",
        "R",
        "S",
        "T",
        "U",
        "V",
        "W",
        "X",
        "Y",
        "Z"
      ],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In hairstyling, what term for the French for “shadow,” means hair with two or more colours that fade gradually into each other from top to bottom?",
      "Answers": ["Ombre"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Gradient"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Grammarians consider there to be eight parts of speech in English: nouns, verbs, pronouns, adjectives, adverbs, conjunction, prepositions, and what last, excitable, part of speech?",
      "Answers": ["Interjections"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Object", "Infinitive", "imperative"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In the NATO Phonetic Alphabet, there are two words that are one syllable: Golf and what other one?",
      "Answers": ["Mike"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Cat", "Zebra", "Two", "Can", "Echo"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": " In phonetics, what “s” is used for a fricative consonant sound, in which the top of the tongue is brought near the roof of the mouth and air is pushed past the tongue to make a hissing sound",
      "Answers": ["Sibilant"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Whispering"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is a sentence that has every letter of a language in it called?",
      "Answers": ["Pangram"],
      "WrongAnswers": [" An alphabet sentence"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "If you want to make sense of ciphertext, you’ll need a key to decrypt it. What’s the name for the readable language text it turns into?",
      "Answers": ["Plaintext"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Plain"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "“Pyjamas,” “scissors,” and “jeans” are English words that only exist in which grammatical form?",
      "Answers": ["Plural"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["constants"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "An international ___ language is one that is meant to help people all over the world communicate with each other even though they don’t speak a common language.",
      "Answers": ["Auxiliary"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Charades", "Sign", " lingua franca"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Braidwoodian system was created by Thomas Braidwood. It was the precursor to British ____ Language.",
      "Answers": ["Sign"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Braille"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which country contains the largest English-speaking population in the world?",
      "Answers": ["India"],
      "WrongAnswers": [" The United States", "China"],
      "Category": "Language"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Macaws are from which family of birds?",
      "Answers": ["Parrots"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Penguins"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the name of the insect which makes honey?",
      "Answers": ["Bee", "Bees"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Wasps"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the name commonly given to the hard protective covering of a crab?",
      "Answers": ["Shell"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Helmet"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What term for a young deer is also a light brown colour?",
      "Answers": ["Fawn"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Dirt", "Tan"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which animals build dams and lodges?",
      "Answers": ["Beaver", "Beavers"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Bears"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which bird gives its name to a straight-legged marching step?",
      "Answers": ["Goose"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Penguin"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the correct name for the Australian wild dog?",
      "Answers": ["Dingo"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Hyena", "Coyote", "Feral", "Mate"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What 'C' is a large North American reindeer?",
      "Answers": ["Caribou"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Crab"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which bodily fluid makes up the major part of the diet of vampire bats?",
      "Answers": ["Blood"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Water"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The llama and alpaca are related to which humped animal of South Asia and North Africa?",
      "Answers": ["Camel"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Hippo"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What insect has many limbs, although the name would suggest that it has one hundred?",
      "Answers": ["Centipede"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Giraffe"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What F is a pink African wading bird?",
      "Answers": ["Flamingo"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Albatross"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": " What name of an amphibian is also the word for the elastic substance in a horse's hoof?",
      "Answers": ["Frog"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Sole", "Rubber", "Keratin"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the largest dolphin of all dolphins?",
      "Answers": ["Orca", "Killer Whale"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["King of the dolphins"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is another name for a North American marsupial?",
      "Answers": ["possum"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["raccoons"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which fish start their lives as male and can change into females as they grow?",
      "Answers": ["Anemone", "clownfish"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Seahorse"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which mammal is known to have the most powerful bite in the world",
      "Answers": ["Hippopotamus", "Hippo"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Crocodile", "Alligator", "Turtle", "Shark"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What object does a male penguin often gifted to a female penguin to win her over?",
      "Answers": ["Pebble", "Rock"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Fish"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many months is an elephant pregnant before it gives birth?",
      "Answers": ["22"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A dog sweats through which part of its body?",
      "Answers": ["Paws"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["skin", "tongue", "eyes"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What colour is the tongue of a giraffe?",
      "Answers": ["Purple", "Black"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Pink", "Red", "White"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which animal’s poop is known to take the shape of cubes?",
      "Answers": ["Wombat"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Armadillo"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Under their white fur, what colour is a polar bear’s skin?",
      "Answers": ["Black"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Brown", "white"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many compartments are in a cow’s stomach?",
      "Answers": ["4"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the name of the fastest land animal?",
      "Answers": ["Cheetah"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Lion", "Tiger", "Ostrich"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A baby goat is called what?",
      "Answers": ["Kid"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Goat"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is a group of kittens called?",
      "Answers": ["Kindle"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["litter", "colony", "Adoption agency"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many humps does a Bactrian camel have?",
      "Answers": ["2"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What name is given to a female deer?",
      "Answers": ["Doe"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Female deer"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What animal is known by the nickname “sea cow”?",
      "Answers": ["Mantee"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["seal", "Sea lion"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What animal is said to have nine lives?",
      "Answers": ["Cat"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["dogs"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What animal eats mainly bamboo?",
      "Answers": ["Panda"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["sloths"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What animal is known to be “man’s best friend”?",
      "Answers": ["Dog"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["cats"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What animal is covered in quills?",
      "Answers": ["Porcupine"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["armadillo"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What kind of turtle can’t retract into its shell?",
      "Answers": ["Sea turtle"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Snapping turtle"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What kind of animal is a Komodo dragon?",
      "Answers": ["Lizard"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Reptile"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What part of a snake does it shed a few times a year?",
      "Answers": ["Skin"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["nose"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What animal breathes out of its butt?",
      "Answers": ["Turtles"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["platypus", "Frogs"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which part of its body does a snake use to smell?",
      "Answers": ["Tongue"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Skin"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Are most reptiles cold-blooded or warm-blooded?",
      "Answers": ["Cold-blooded"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["warm-blooded"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What’s the name of the largest snake in the world?",
      "Answers": ["Anaconda"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["King Cobra", "Python"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What type of reptile can detach its tail when it’s in danger and then regrow it",
      "Answers": ["Lizard"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["wolf"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the three-letter name of the second-tallest (standing) bird on the planet?",
      "Answers": ["Emu"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["ostrich"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which insect gets its name from the Spanish word for “little fly”?",
      "Answers": ["Mosquito"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Gnat"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many fingers does a raccoon have on each front paw?",
      "Answers": ["5"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Found in mostly Asia, the macaque is a type of animal?",
      "Answers": ["Monkey"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Bear", "Bird"],
      "Category": "Wildlife"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In the human body what is the name of the main olfactory organ?",
      "Answers": ["Nose"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Mitochondria"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A human adult has how many wisdom teeth?",
      "Answers": ["Four"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "0"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In the human body, insulin and adrenaline are types of what?",
      "Answers": ["Hormone"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Enzymes"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What 'V' is a dilute acetic acid and is used as a condiment",
      "Answers": ["Vinegar"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Bicarbonate of soda"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the name of the part of the brain in the frontal lobe that is heavily involved in speech?",
      "Answers": ["Broca's Area"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Hippocampus"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Anoxic means that which element needed by most life to survive is absent?",
      "Answers": ["Oxygen"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Water"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The rare condition of a dorsal cutaneous appendage on a human being is more commonly known as what four-letter vestigial body part?",
      "Answers": ["Tail"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Hand", "Feet"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Waxy buildup in the human ear is actually a form of what moisture exuded from pores on the skin?",
      "Answers": ["Sweat"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Mucus", "Oil"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "All amino acids contain carbon, hydrogen, oxygen, and what other element that starts and ends with the same letter?",
      "Answers": ["Nitrogen"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Oxygen"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Organ transplants in the United States are dominated by one organ, which is involved in over 50% of all organ transplants that occur. What organ is this?",
      "Answers": ["Kidney"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Liver"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The goal of any operating room is what “A” term, the state of being free from contamination from bacteria, viruses, or other microorganisms?",
      "Answers": ["Aseptic"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Asphyxiation"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What five-letter word means a single-celled reproductive unit that is capable of giving rise to a new organism without sexual fusion, such as those found in fungi?",
      "Answers": ["Spore"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Virus"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Metabolic reactions can be described as \"anabolic,\" or what other term, which refers to reactions in which energy is released by the breaking down of compounds?",
      "Answers": ["Catabolic"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Aerobic"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What \"A\" word in cell biology means the period in mitosis or meiosis in which chromosomes move away from one another to opposite poles of the spindle?",
      "Answers": ["Anaphase"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["analog"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "BRCA1 is a human gene and protein pairing most commonly associated with what disease?",
      "Answers": ["Breast Cancer"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Diabetes"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In DNA, the four nucleotide bases are adenine, cytosine, guanine, and thymine; in RNA, what base replaces thymine?",
      "Answers": ["Uracil"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["U"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What’s  the term for an organism that loves and thrives in an environment with a pH under 4?",
      "Answers": ["Acidophile"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Extremophiles"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What marine invertebrate typically lives in a compact colony composed of many identical, individual polyps?",
      "Answers": ["Coral"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Jellyfish", "Sea urchin"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Pathogenicity means the ability of an infectious organism to cause disease; what V-word means the severity of the symptoms it causes?",
      "Answers": ["Virulence"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Vulnerability"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What “v” is the name of the infectious entities affecting plants that are smaller than viruses and consist only of nucleic acid without a protein coat?",
      "Answers": ["Viroids"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["virus"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What “i” refers to the attachment between a newly born organism and its caretaker? ",
      "Answers": ["Imprinting"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Intelligence", "Umbilical cord"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In which subdiscipline of microbiology would you study marimo, giant kelp, and other algae?",
      "Answers": ["Phycology"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Paleoanthropology", "Paleobiology", "Paleobotany"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Hydrolysis is the process of using which substance to break down polymers into smaller molecules?",
      "Answers": ["Water"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Oxygen"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What “P” “-ology” describes the study of eukaryotic organisms that do not classify as plant, animal or fungus?",
      "Answers": ["Protistology"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Paleoanthropology", "Paleobiology", "Paleobotany"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which light-producing enzyme can occur naturally in organisms such as fireflies?",
      "Answers": ["Luciferase"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Light"],
      "Category": "Biology"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Maths, 'proper' and 'vulgar' are types of what number?",
      "Answers": ["Fractions"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Whole"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What imperial length is the equivalent to eight furlongs?",
      "Answers": ["Mile"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["foot"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A century celebrates how many years of a particular event?",
      "Answers": ["100"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many units are there in a dozen?",
      "Answers": ["12"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Immediately before (UK) decimalisation, there were how many shillings to a pound?",
      "Answers": ["20"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["12"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In Roman numerals,  what number is represented by the letters IX?",
      "Answers": ["9"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["11"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the highest double-figured number?",
      "Answers": ["99"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["25"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the next prime number after 7?",
      "Answers": ["11"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["13"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is 65 minus 43?",
      "Answers": ["22"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What comes at the end of this pattern: million, billion, trillion?",
      "Answers": ["Quadrillion"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["quintillion"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many sides does a nonagon have?",
      "Answers": ["9"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the next number in the Fibonacci sequence: 0, 1, 1, 2, 3, 5, 8, 13, 21, 34 ?",
      "Answers": ["55"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What does 5 to the power of 0 equal to?",
      "Answers": ["1"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["5", "0"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many zeros are in 1 billion?",
      "Answers": ["9"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["12"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many metres are there in a kilometre?",
      "Answers": ["1000"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["10", "100"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What’s 3/4 of 56?",
      "Answers": ["42"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The roman numeral of LX is equivalent to what number?",
      "Answers": ["60"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In the UK, how many teaspoons does it take to equal a tablespoon?",
      "Answers": ["3"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many seconds are in 200 minutes?",
      "Answers": ["12000"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1200", "12000"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In trigonometry, what is the reciprocal of cosine?",
      "Answers": ["Secant"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["sin"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Moving clockwise on a clock’s face, what number is 90 degrees from the 12?",
      "Answers": ["3"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["9", "6"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the square root of 256?",
      "Answers": ["16"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which is longer: 1 month or 1000 hours?",
      "Answers": ["1000 hours"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1 month"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is longer: 10 inches or 20 centimetres?",
      "Answers": ["10 inches"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["20 centimetres"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many total days are in November and December combined?",
      "Answers": ["61"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many are in a baker’s dozen?",
      "Answers": ["13"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1", "2", "3", "4", "5", "6", "7", "8", "9"],
      "Category": "Maths"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Cantaloupe, Galia and Honeydew are types of which fruit?",
      "Answers": ["Melon"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Grapefruits", "Orange"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the name for six children born to a mother at the same time?",
      "Answers": ["Sextuplets"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Quintuplets"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What two words does a drill-sergeant use to make marching troops turn around?",
      "Answers": ["About Turn"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Reverse March"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In athletics in which discipline does the competitor hold a metal ball under their chin before throwing it?",
      "Answers": ["Shot-Putt", "Shot Putt"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Discus"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which lively dance is the first name for a spotted pattern on fabric?",
      "Answers": ["Polka"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Calico"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "A clog is worn on which part of the body?",
      "Answers": ["Foot"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["The bottom"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What word connected to drum, disc and air is associated with slowing down a vehicle?",
      "Answers": ["Brake"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Gun"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Donkeys and other load-bearing animals are known as 'beasts of ..' what?",
      "Answers": ["Burden"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Power"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Cotton buds carry a warning not to insert them into which part of the body?",
      "Answers": ["Ears"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Eyes"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In religion a customary expression refers to 'The Father..' and which other relative?",
      "Answers": ["Son"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Ghost"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In the game 'scissors, paper, stone', what beats paper?",
      "Answers": ["Scissors"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Stone"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What item in the kitchen might include an interior light, automatic defrost, and an egg-rack?",
      "Answers": ["Fridge"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Microwave"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What word can mean a space-craft, a firework, and a severe reprimand?",
      "Answers": ["Rocket"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Shuttle"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What fruit juice is in a pina colada?",
      "Answers": ["Pineapple"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Mango"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In the Olympics what event includes the parallel bars and the high bar?",
      "Answers": ["Gymnastics"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["The pentathlon"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Fisherman's pie is a dish topped with which mashed vegetable?",
      "Answers": ["Potato"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Cabbage"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is fixed into window frames using putty?",
      "Answers": ["Glass"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Cement"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the acronym for 'Double Income No Kids Yet'?",
      "Answers": ["DINKY"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["DKNY"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "It is customary for Roman Catholics eat fish on which day of the week?",
      "Answers": ["Friday"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Tuesday"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which type of punishment shares its name with a rank in the army?",
      "Answers": ["Corporal"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Capital"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the last letter of the Greek alphabet?",
      "Answers": ["Omega"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Z"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which beverage has varieties including latte and mocha?",
      "Answers": ["Coffee"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Milk"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What word beginning with 'G' is the area of medicine specialising in the treatment of the elderly?",
      "Answers": ["Geriatrics"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Gynaecology"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which Cluedo character has a military rank?",
      "Answers": ["Colonel Mustard"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Colonel Sanders"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What does the acronym NASA stand for?",
      "Answers": ["National Aeronautics and Space Administration"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["National Socialist Space Satellite"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In nature, cumulus and cirrus are types of what?",
      "Answers": ["Cloud"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Lion"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which European language do the words Blitz, Kindergarten and Angst come from?",
      "Answers": ["German"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Italian"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The name of which famous racehorse was the word 'murder' spelt backwards?",
      "Answers": ["Red Rum"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Shergar"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": " what language, spoken in part of the United Kingdom, was the hymn 'Guide Me O Thou Great Redeemer' originally written?",
      "Answers": ["Gaelic"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Islam"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What is the name of the 1994 Oscar winning film which starred Ben Kingsley as Yitzak Stern?",
      "Answers": ["Schindler's List"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Gandhi"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In what European country was actor Antonio Banderas born?",
      "Answers": ["Spain"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Mexico"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What 'Z' is used to describe a human who has returned from the dead?",
      "Answers": ["Zombie"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Unicorn"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which 'C' is a food colouring made from insects from South America which live in cactus plants?",
      "Answers": ["Cochineal"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Crab"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": " What was the principal language used by the ancient Romans?",
      "Answers": ["Latin"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Greek"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The maxim 'Thou shall not get found out' is commonly known as the eleventh what?",
      "Answers": ["Commandment"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Hour"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In language the cockney rhyming slang for road is 'Frog and...' what?",
      "Answers": ["Toad"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Pears"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Wholegrain, Dijon and English are varieties of which condiment",
      "Answers": ["Mustard"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Rice"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In law the principle that a person cannot be tried twice for the same offence is called 'Double...' what?",
      "Answers": ["Jeopardy"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Whammy"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Uncle Sam is said to represent the USA, whereas John who represents Britain?",
      "Answers": ["Bull"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Peel"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The chef known for his Caribbean food is Levi who?",
      "Answers": ["Roots"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Strauss"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What girl's name is a term for a short prayer or thanks before a meal?",
      "Answers": ["Grace"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Mary"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What T is the name of the person who made decorative glassware and lamps?",
      "Answers": ["Tiffany"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Trotsky"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The nickname of the Duke of Wellington included which metallic element?",
      "Answers": ["Iron"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Fire"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Apart from Earth, which planet in our solar system begins with a vowel?",
      "Answers": ["Uranus"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Pluto"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "When spoken by a German, which letter does the letter W sound like?",
      "Answers": ["V"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["H"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What sport do you play on grass with rackets?",
      "Answers": ["Tennis", "Badminton"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Cricket"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Mouldy cheese and the blood of aristocrats are said to be which colour?",
      "Answers": ["Blue"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Purple"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Traditionally what liquid is said to be poured on troubled waters?",
      "Answers": ["Oil"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Cold Water"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What very common five-letter surname is the word for a metal-worker?",
      "Answers": ["Smith"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Jones"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The trimming of the clothes worn by Santa Claus is traditionally what colour?",
      "Answers": ["White"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Red"],
      "Category": "Other"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who became US president when Nixon resigned?",
      "Answers": ["Gerald Ford"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Bill Gates", "Bill Clinton"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Juan Peron was the president of which South American country?",
      "Answers": ["Argentina"],
      "WrongAnswers": [" Brazil", "Peru", "Chile"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who became manager of Manchester United in 1986?",
      "Answers": ["Alex Ferguson"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "Erik ten Hag",
        "Ralf Rangnick",
        "Michael Carrick",
        "Ole Gunnar Solskjaer",
        "Jose Mourinho"
      ],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "John Glenn was the first man from which country to orbit the Earth?",
      "Answers": ["USA", "United States", "United States of America"],
      "WrongAnswers": [" Germany", "Russia"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which Indian leader, whose last name began with 'G', took the name Mahatma? ",
      "Answers": ["Gandhi"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "Mikhail Gorbachev",
        "Ulysses S. Grant",
        "Muammar Gaddafi",
        "Joseph Goebbels"
      ],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which calendar month was named after the first Roman Emperor?",
      "Answers": ["August"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "January",
        "February",
        "March",
        "April",
        "May",
        "June",
        "July",
        "September",
        "October",
        "November",
        "December"
      ],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What was the last state to join the USA?",
      "Answers": ["Hawaii"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["New York", "Ohio", "Georgia"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What man-made structure built during the 3rd century B.C. is often said to be visible from space?",
      "Answers": ["The Great Wall Of China"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Great Pyramid of Giza", "Petra", "Machu Picchu"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which musician famous for playing the piano honky-tonk style died in the year 2000?",
      "Answers": ["Winifred Atwell"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Ray Charles", "Stevie Wonder"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Pakistan was part of which other state until it achieved independence in 1947?",
      "Answers": ["India"],
      "WrongAnswers": [
        "Japan",
        "Indonesia",
        "China",
        "South Korea",
        "Thailand"
      ],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Battle of Rourke's Drift was between the British and which indigenous people of South Africa?",
      "Answers": ["Zulus"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Aborigines "],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Mexican War was fought over a border dispute with which other country?",
      "Answers": ["USA", "United States", "United States of America"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Spain"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In America, the 18th century protestation about taxes was called 'The Boston..' what?",
      "Answers": ["Tea-Party"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Uprising"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The United States bought Alaska from which country?",
      "Answers": ["Russia"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Germany", "United Kingdom", "France", "Italy", "Spain"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who was the fourth president of the United States?",
      "Answers": ["James Madison"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["James Monroe", "Qunincy Adams"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Fill in the blank: The 19th Amendment guarantees ____ the right to vote.",
      "Answers": ["Women"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Corporations", "Black people", "Criminals"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who was president during the Cuban Missile Crisis?",
      "Answers": ["John F. Kennedy", "JFK"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Lydon B Johsnon", "KFC"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What year did the French Revolution start?",
      "Answers": ["1789"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1812", "1792", "1728"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In what year did Libya gain independence from Italy?",
      "Answers": ["1951"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1922", "1937", "2023"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Where did Albert Einstein live before moving to the United States?",
      "Answers": ["Germany"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Switzerland", "Poaland", "Austria"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How old was Queen Elizabeth II when she was crowned the Queen of England?",
      "Answers": ["27"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["80", "72", "20"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who was the first ruler of the Mongol Empire?",
      "Answers": ["Genghis Khan"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Donkey Kong"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In which country was the Battle of Culloden fought in 1746?",
      "Answers": ["Scotland"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["South Sudan", "Israel", "Switzerland"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who was the first Emperor of Rome?",
      "Answers": ["Augustus Caesar"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Julius Caesar"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which Greek goddess was the Parthenon dedicated to?",
      "Answers": ["Athena"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Aphrodite"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Great Pyramid was built as a tomb for which pharaoh?",
      "Answers": ["Khufu"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Ra", "Tut", "Ramses the Second"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who established the Xia Dynasty in China?",
      "Answers": ["Yu the Great"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Qin Shi Huang"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who is the king of the Olympian gods in Greek mythology?",
      "Answers": ["Zeus"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Hades", "Poseidon"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The Maya Empire was centred in what is now which country?",
      "Answers": ["Guatemala"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Mexico"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which ancient figure is often considered the founder of Western philosophy?",
      "Answers": ["Socrates"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Aristotle", "Plateau"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How old was King Tutankhamun when he died?",
      "Answers": ["19"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["13", "50", "55"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which fabric was invented in Ancient China?",
      "Answers": ["Silk"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Velvet", "Flannel", "Chiffon", "Silk"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What was the acronym commonly used for the 2000 software problem that many thought would cause computers to become inoperable?",
      "Answers": ["Y2K"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["2k23"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which country hosted the 2016 Olympics?",
      "Answers": ["Brazil"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Argentina", "COlombia", "Peru", "Chile", "Ecuador"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The U.S. rover Curiosity landed on which planet in August 2012?",
      "Answers": ["Mars"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Earth", "Jupiter", "Saturn"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What year did the Berlin Wall fall?",
      "Answers": ["1989"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1991"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What was the name of the Category 5 hurricane that hit New Orleans and its surrounding areas in 2005?",
      "Answers": ["Katrina"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Emily", "Bret", "Dorian"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "The U.S. hosted the FIFA World Cup in 1994. Which country won the game?",
      "Answers": ["Brazil"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Argentina"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Which planet was downgraded to a dwarf planet in 2006?",
      "Answers": ["Pluto"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Earth", "Jupiter", "Saturn"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who won the 2008 U.S. Presidential election?",
      "Answers": ["Barack Obama", "Obama"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Bill Clinton", "Hilairy Clinton"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "What year was Nelson Mandela freed from prison?",
      "Answers": ["1990"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["2013"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Who was the first woman to be elected Vice President of the United States in 2020?",
      "Answers": ["Kamala Harris"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Serina Williams"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "How many years did the 100 years war last?",
      "Answers": ["116"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["98", "4", "150"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In which year did Hitler commit suicide?",
      "Answers": ["1945"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1922", "1932", "1939"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "In which year was John F. Kennedy assassinated?",
      "Answers": ["1963"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["1962"],
      "Category": "History"
    },
    {
      "Question": "Greenland was a colony of which country until 1981?",
      "Answers": ["Denmark"],
      "WrongAnswers": ["Norway", "Netherlands", "Germany", "Sweden", "Belgium"],
      "Category": "History"
    }
  ]
};